<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spoken Language Recognition on Ivan Kukanov | Personal Page</title>
    <link>https://vanova.github.io/tags/spoken-language-recognition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spoken Language Recognition on Ivan Kukanov | Personal Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vanova.github.io/tags/spoken-language-recognition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximal Figure-of-Merit Framework to Detect Multi-label Phonetic Features for Spoken Language Recognition</title>
      <link>https://vanova.github.io/publication/2019/pub3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vanova.github.io/publication/2019/pub3/</guid>
      <description>Bottleneck features (BNFs) generated with a deep neural network (DNN) have proven to boost spoken language recognition accuracy over basic spectral features significantly. However, BNFs are commonly extracted using language-dependent tied-context phone states as learning targets. Moreover, BNFs are less phonetically expressive than the output layer in a DNN, which is usually not used as a speech feature because of its very high dimensionality hindering further post-processing. In this article, we put forth a novel deep learning framework to overcome all of the above issues and evaluate it on the 2017 NIST Language Recognition Evaluation (LRE) challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 2015 NIST Language Recognition Evaluation: the Shared View of I2R, Fantastic4 and SingaMS</title>
      <link>https://vanova.github.io/publication/2016/pub5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vanova.github.io/publication/2016/pub5/</guid>
      <description>The series of language recognition evaluations (LRE’s) conducted by the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) have been one of the driving forces in advancing spoken language recognition technology. This paper presents a shared view of five institutions resulting from our collaboration toward LRE 2015 submissions under the names of I2R, Fantastic4, and SingaMS. Among others, LRE’15 emphasizes on language detection in the context of closely related languages, which is different from previous LRE’s.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>